{
  "assessment" : [
    {
      "question" : "Which data structure maintains the insertion order in Python ",
      "options": ["List", "Dictionary", "Set", "Tuple"],
      "answer" : "List"
    },
    {
      "question" : "A __________ is the only data structure that uses key-value pairs.",
      "options": ["List", "Set", "Tuple", "Dictionary"],
      "answer" : "Dictionary"
    },
    {
      "question" : "A dictionary key can be any mutable object. ",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer" : "False"
    },
    {
      "question" : "Which data structure provides the fastest way to check if an item exists using keys?",
      "options": ["List", "Set", "Tuple", "Dictionary"],
      "answer" : "Dictionary"
    },
    {
      "question" : "Which data structure should be used when data must not be modified after creation?",
      "options": ["List", "Set", "Tuple", "Dictionary"],
      "answer" : "Tuple"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the key difference between a list and a tuple?",
      "options" : ["Lists are immutable, but tuples are mutable", "Tuples are immutable, but lists are mutable ", "Both are immutable", "Lists are ordered, but tuples are unordered"],
      "answer" : "Tuples are immutable, but lists are mutable "
    },
    {
      "question" : "Which data structure does NOT support indexing?",
      "options": ["List", "Set", "Tuple", "Dictionary"],
      "answer" : "Set"
    },
    {
      "question" : "Which data structure would be best for storing unique student roll numbers efficiently?",
      "options": ["List", "Set", "Tuple", "Dictionary"],
      "answer" : "Set"
    },
    {
      "question" : "Sets store elements in an unordered way.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer" : "True"
    },
    {
      "question" : "A dictionary can have duplicate keys",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "answer" : "False"
    },
    {
      "question" : "If you need to store a sequence of items and prioritize iteration speed, which data structure is best?",
      "options": ["List", "Set", "Tuple", "Dictionary"],
      "answer" : "Tuple"
    }
  ]
}